http://www.probet.info/privacy/

Return to previous pageHome
Privacy
Privacy PolicyBelow is our policy relating to the ways we collect and manage your Personal Information.Your rights to privacy as well as the requirements relating to collection, management and disclosure of your Personal Information are set out under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (“Act”). Please visit www.oaic.gov.au for more informationYour Personal InformationThe term “Personal Information” (when used in this policy) has the meaning given to it under the Act.  It generally includes any information that can be used to identify you personally.  Such information may include your name, occupation, address, telephone number or email address. Information will be considered Personal Information if the information collected by us identifies you personally, or you are reasonably identifiable from it.Collection of Personal InformationPersonal Information we may collect includesName Phone Number Email AddressCredit Card DetailsOther information we have asked on web page and you have provided us.Personal Information is collected directly from you unless it is unreasonable or impracticable to do so. We may collect Personal information in ways including (but not limited to) through:1. your accessing and use of our website;2. conversations between you.3. your online purchases4. your enquiries for further information on products or services, or by registering your details on our website.5. subscribing to our mailing list6. providing information via our social media pages (Facebook or Twitter).Information from third parties such as credit reporting agencies, law enforcement agencies, and other government agencies may also be collected.If we Cannot collect your Personal Information?If you do not provide us with the Personal Information described above, the following instances may happen:1. we may not be able to provide the requested products or services to you.2. we may not be able to provide you with information about our specific productsReasons for collecting, holding, using and disclosing your Personal InformationWe collect and hold your information to understand your needs better and provide you with better service. We may share your Personal Information amongst Related Bodies Corporate as defined in the Corporations Act 2001 (Cth). We may also use, collect, hold and disclose your Personal Information:1. The purposes of completing a transaction online via our website.2. Your questions or customer service issues.3. When responding to social media;4. Giving you access to specific areas of our websitePersonal Information will not be shared, sold, rented or disclosed other than as described in this Privacy Policy.Disclosing your Personal InformationYour Personal Information may be disclosed by us to:1. Service providers for the purposes of operating our business and website, fulfilling requests made by you.Marketing InformationWe may contact you about other services that you could have an interest in.  They will be sent via email or social media, in accordance with applicable laws, such as the Spam Act 2003 (Cth). You can ask to be removed from all marketing at any time.We do not provide your Personal Information to other organizations for the purposes of direct marketing.Breach of privacyIf you believe your privacy has been breached, please contact us and provide details of what’s occurred so that it can be investigated.Links to other websitesLinks to any third party websites on our website are provided solely as a convenience to you. Using these links will result in you leaving the relevant ProBet site and we hold no responsibility for any third party websites, their content or their usage of your Personal Information.SecurityWe will take all reasonable precautions to ensure the security of your Personal Information and protect this information from loss, alteration or misuse.Changes to Privacy PolicyWe may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Changes will be published on our website.This policy was last updated on May 5th 2020Email ; david@probet.info
Design and website built by Barrett Design
© Copyright 2020 Probet | Privacy Policy and Terms
